Aditya Prawira

Software Developer

A curious software developer with 1+ years of experience in a fast and dynamic development team environment. Aiming to apply proven skills and continuously learn new technology stack in improving human productivity through a piece of software.

CONTACTS

Phone

0402 555 502

Email

adityaprawira96@gmail.com

Location

Melbourne, Australia

GitHub

https://github.com/adit-prawira

Website

https://adityaprawira.herokuapp.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aditya-prawira

SKILLS

Database

PostgreSQL, PostGIS, MongoDB

Programming Language

Typescript/Javascript, Python, Java, C++

Tech Stack

NodeJS, NestJS, Express, ReactJS, React Native, ReduxJS, Redux Toolkit, Jōtai, Docker, Kubernetes, AWS, CircleCl, GitlabCl, Jest, Material-Ul, grommet, Rest API, GraphQL, and Mapbox.

AWARDS

Team Member of the Month (09/2021) - Award for developing an automation software project used by the internal team for marketing purposes, reaching clients and meeting deadlines.

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent) and Indonesian (Native)

WORK EXPERIENCES

Laputan Software, Melbourne — Software Developer

April 2022 - PRESENT

- Working with more than 5 technologies such as React, Redux-Saga, Typescript, GraphQL, Docker, and more.
- Develop serverless REST API and GraphQL with AWS lambda. Implement design patterns that improve the development process by 20%.

University of Melbourne, Melbourne — Junior Full-stack Software Engineer

March 2022 - PRESENT

- Developed software for PeakHour Urban Technologies startup company and worked with more than 5 technologies such as Typescript, AWS, Docker, NestJS, React, etc.
- Data processing on large datasets to build server-side ML model with a performance 48.07% faster than expected. Deploy more than 4 features for both server-side and client-side.
- Developing software for processing and rendering GTFS data.

Reesby, Melbourne — Front End Team Lead Intern

December 2021 - April 2022

- Selected as the top-performing intern 4 times by the technology team. Software testing for bugs and operating speed.
- Bugs fixing and documenting processes to increase efficiency by 18%.

Reesby, Melbourne — Front End Developer Intern

June 2021 - December 2021

- Developed a marketing tool that enables the organisation to reach a total of 24,786 clients for an organisation's event with one click of a button with React and Redux.
- Increase the delivery rate by 25% by developing a CI/CD pipeline from version control to AWS.

EDUCATIONS

RMIT University, Melbourne — *Master of Engineering (Robotics and Mechatronics Engineering)*

July 2020 - July 2022

- Final grade of GPA of 3.4 out of 4.
- Develop computer vision software and ML model for dairy cow action recognition as a final year project.

University of Melbourne, Melbourne — *Bachelor of Science (Mechanical System)*

July 2017 - July 2020

- A team of 4 developing a 3D CAD simulation for Warman Competition 2020 for the final year project. The final design is predicted to be in the top 5 by a professional engineer.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Face-Identity Computer Vision Project

November 2021 - December 2021

- Develop a human-computer interaction (HCI) face identification system backed by monolith API using Django, SQL, and AWS S3. (https://github.com/adit-prawira/face attendance server)
- Data acquisition with OpenCV and Google Voice Assistant integration for the voice user interface (VUI). Utilise multi-threading and message queue. (https://github.com/adit-prawira/face-attendance)

Kinesis Project

October 2021 - January 2022

- A fitness React native mobile app built with Typescript and backed with ExpressJS server, MongoDB Atlas, S3, and CircleCI. (https://github.com/adit-prawira/kinesis)